<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on PrestaShop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 11:32:43 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>System requirements for PrestaShop 1.7</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>System requirements for PrestaShop 1.7 PrestaShop needs the following server configuration in order to run:
 System: Unix, Linux or Windows. Web server: Apache Web Server 2.2 or any later version. PHP:   1.7.0~1.7.3  PHP 5.4 or later  1.7.4  PHP 5.6 or later  MySQL: 5.0 or later. Server RAM: The more the better…  PrestaShop can also work with Microsoft’s IIS Web server 6.0 or later, and nginx 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/basics/installation/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuring PrestaShop By default, PrestaShop is configured to provide a secure and stable environment to both the shop administrator and the customers.
As a developer, there are several changes that you could and should bring to the default installation in order to help you code better, spot bugs faster, and generally make a great PrestaShop product.
Disabling the cache and forcing Smarty compilation When your development has an impact on the front office, whether you are building a theme or simply a module which displays information to the customer, you should force the template file compilation and disable the cache, so as to always see the result of your changes directly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>